klixdigital.com 2014-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Klix Digital

This website is provided by Klix Digital. We take very seriously the privacy of our website users and the security of personal information. So we have developed this Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please note that when you enter any sub-site accessible through this homepage, such sub-site may have its own terms and conditions of use which are specific to such sub-site. So please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Information Collection**  
The site may ask you to provide information that could be used to identify you personally, such as name; e-mail; telephone number; mobile phone number; or home address. For example, Klix Digital may collect your personal information when you register to receive newsletters; send questions or comments; or otherwise communicate or interact with us. Please note that information submitted to the site via a “contact us” or other similar function may not receive a response. We will not use the information provided to contact you for marketing purposes unrelated to your request unless you agree otherwise.

Klix Digital also automatically collects your IP address or other unique identifier that is called “Device Identifier” for the computer, mobile device, technology, or other device you use to access the site. Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your device when you access a web site or its servers, and our computers identify your device by its Device Identifier. 

Whenever you visit or interact with the site, Klix Digital, as well as any third-party advertisers and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the site are accessed and used, also called “Usage Information”. It may include browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, and the preceding page views. Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if Klix Digital associates it with you as a specific and identifiable person, Klix Digital treats it as personal information.

**Information Use**  
Klix Digital may use collected information, including personal information, in order to: (1) allow you to participate in offered features on the site; (2) process your registration, including to verify that the e-mail address you provide is active; (3) provide you with information that you have agreed or requested to receive; (4) develop the site for internal purposes such as data analysis and research in order to improve services and customer communications; (5) contact you with regard to your use of the site, your account, or changes to any Klix Digital policy.

**Security**  
Klix Digital has a commitment to ensure the security of your information through the use of appropriate technology and internal procedures. Klix Digital takes precautions, including technical; physical; electronic; and managerial measures, to safeguard your personal information against loss; theft; and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access; disclosure; alteration; and destruction.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps you to analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can gather and record information about your preferences.

Overall, cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. Cookies help us to provide a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. Cookies in no way give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

Users can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full features of the site.

**Privacy Questions**  
If you have any questions; comments; or concerns about Klix Digital’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please feel free to send us an email at [info@klixdigital.com](mailto:info@klixdigital.com).
